Hi everyone from Malta! I'm here for a week of vacation but I also visited the
Dark Malta festival. I did a festival report and vlog you can see here and
today I took all my swimsuits, I packed in my suitcase and went over there to
film a alternative swimwear try on or haul video because I think we need more
fashion on the beach and I'm going to show you my favorites.
Thank you.
The water is so cold, like it hurts, it's so cold.
I didn't expect that and I'm definitely not going to swim.
So it's April, the sea is cold.
Now I have to get back outside and the floor is clean and it hurts.
I'm seeking sanctuary
You never guess the things that I do
I've had the devil around me too
Don't you know that I'm here beside you
Can't you see that I can't relax
When I saw you in my rear view
You could have stopped me in my tracks
I'll be there for you when you want me to
I'll stand by your side like I always do
In the dead of night it'll be alright
Cause I'll be there for you when you want me to
You could take me to an island
Right across a stormy sea
Where you see
Hey!
Small blackfishies, so fun.
It's a pool here with all the rocks.
The water isn't as cold here as it was at the other spot.
I don't know why, maybe I'm used to it.
Thank you.